谁在鬼叫
What the hell is that?
谁在鬼叫  是你吗
What the hell is that? Is that you?
你还真不是个早起的人  一边去
Boy, you're really not a morning person. Just back off!
起床  起床  起床
Get up! Get up! Get up!
什么声音
What is that noise?
你的敲门声
You.
是小鸡啦
It's the chick.
她...有了些变化
She's going through some changes.
什么变化
What kind of changes?
兽医认为小母鸡要变成公鸡了
Well, the vet seems to think that she's becoming a rooster.
我们打算再问问别的兽医
We're getting a second opinion.
老友记  第四季  第12集  受精卵
Friends S04E12  The One With The Embryos
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
你干嘛早晨八点就去购物血拼了
Hey, what are you doing shopping at 8 in the morning?
我6点钟就起床了
Well, I've been up since 6...
多谢某人的臭公鸡
...thanks to somebody's dumb-ass rooster.
你们应该把它们处理掉
You guys, you really should get rid of those animals.
不应该窝在公寓里
They shouldn't be in an apartment.
对  尤其是应该远离那些餐刀和食谱
Yeah! Especially not with all of these knives and cookbooks around
我要去看妇产科医生  看看我是否准备好
All right, I'm gonna go to the fertility doctor and, uh, see if I'm ready...
把法兰克和艾莉丝的胚胎  移植到我的子宫里去
...to have Frank and Alice's embryo transferred into my uterus.
他们怎么知道你准备好了没有
Now, how will they know if you're ready?
哦  只是看看我的子宫内膜是不是变厚了
Oh, they're just gonna look and see if my endometrial layer is thick.
哦  我能帮你检查这个
Oh, I can check that for you.
好的  各位  帮我的子宫内膜加油吧
Okay, everyone, think "thick."
再见  祝你好运
Good-bye! Good luck.
嗨  祝我好运
Hey. Wish me luck. Hey.
哦  祝你好运  祝你好运
Oh, good luck. Good luck.
我说得没错啦  不对
And I'm still right. so not true.
什么
What?
她不爽是因为我知道  今天是洗衣服日子
She's mad because I know today's her laundry day...
导演：凯文布莱特
所以现在穿的是老女人才穿的那种大内裤
...and that means she's wearing her old-lady underpants.
我能帮你检查这个
I can check that for you.
我只是不相信  你和钱德了解我和瑞秋
I just can't believe that you think that you and Chandler know me and Rachel...
比我们了解你们更深
...better than we know you.
没错  本来就是
Well, we do.
你吃薄荷糖时一定要吃偶数
You can only eat Tic Tacs in even numbers.
对  这说明什么
Yeah, what's that about?
而你  罗斯  我相信  你去搜搜瑞秋的购物袋
And you. Ross, I believe if you check Rachel's bag...
里面一定有一盒  吃了一半的饼干
...you will find a half-eaten box of cookies in there.
你厉害
You're good.
这饼干可不怎么样
These are not.
有什么了不起  哪有人买东西时不吃零嘴
I'm so not impressed. Everybody snacks when they shop.
是么  嗯
Yeah. Oh, yeah?
罗斯  看看袋子里还有多少样东西
Ross, how many items left in that bag?
五样  好的
Five. Okay.
赌十块  我们能说出里面每样东西
Ten bucks says that we can name every item in that bag.
你们能猜几次  六次
How many guesses do you get? Six.
男生队挑战
Challenge extended.
赌就赌  女生队接受桃战
Deal. Challenge accepted.
好吧  首先是…苹果
All right, we'll start with......apples.
我们猜首先是苹果
We'll be starting with apples.
别这样
Stop that now.
没错
Yes.
好  呃  玉米片
Okay. Uh, tortilla chips.
优格  健怡汽水
Yogurt. Diet soda.
有  有  有
Yes, yes, yes.
柳橙汁  错  里面没有柳橙汁
Orange juice. No, there's no orange juice in there.
我们赢了  哈哈
We win. Ha, ha.
他们还有一次机会猜
They have another guess.
但是那题我们赢了
Okay, well, we won that one.
最后一样东西是
Okay. The last thing is...
喔  喔  喔
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
不  不  还要等两周
No, no. Not for, like, another two weeks.
我知道了  透-明
I got it. Scotch...
胶-带
...tape.
你怎么知道她会买胶带
How did you know she would buy Scotch tape?
我们昨晚玩扮鬼脸时  把她们的胶带用光了
Well, we used up theirs last night making scary faces.
你们
Oh, man.
好吧  十块钱  愿赌服输
All right. Ten bucks. Fork it over.
快交钱  拿钱来
Cough it up. Pay the piper.
给我
Give me it.
这不表示你们了解我们更深  我要再比一次
That does not mean you know us better. I want a rematch.
对  而且不是这些没有挑战性的问题  真正的个人问题
Yeah, and none of these stupid grocery questions. Real personal questions.
对  赢了赌一百块
Yeah. And the winner gets 100 bucks.
当真
Serious?
怕了吧
Are you scared?
不
No.
好的  谁来出题
Okay, who makes up the questions?
罗斯会出
Ross will do it.
哦  当然  罗斯会出
Oh, sure, Ross will do it.
反正他没工作  没儿子  生活又无聊
It's not like he has a job or a child or a life of his own.
好嘛   那找菲比好了
Well, fine. We'll ask Phoebe.
不  不  不  我想玩嘛
No, no, no, I wanna play.
看上去你的子宫已经完全可以做胚胎移植了
Looks like your uterus is ready for implantation.
哦  我就知道  我就知道  我今天早上就觉得厚厚的
Oh, I knew it. I knew it. I felt really thick this morning.
好的  现在怎么办  快去拿卵子放进去吧
Ha, ha. Okay, so, what's now? Go get the eggs. Put them in there.
准备那些胚胎要花点时间
Okay. It'll take just a little while to prepare the embryos.
那些胚胎  不止一个  事实上  一共有五个
Embryos? As in more than one? Mm-hm. Five, actually.
五个  那我生的时候
Five? Okay, where am I giving birth
去医院还是要准备个大盒子
in a hospital or a big box under the stairs?
植入五个胚胎  表示着床机率大概是25%
Ha, ha. We do five because that gives you a 25-percent chance...that at least one will attach.
25%这么少
That's it? Twenty-five percent?
也就是说有75%的可能根本就没有孩子
That means that it's, like, 75-percent chance of no baby at all?
嘿  我想  要是放进200个胚胎
Yeah, you know, I was thinking, what are the odds
那成功的机会是多少
if, like, you stuff, like, 200 of them in there?
亲爱的
Sweetie, now...
她是个女人 不是卖泡泡糖的机器
she's a woman, not a gumball machine.
别担心 我会一直做到成功为止
Okay, well, you know what? Don't worry.
因为我可以帮你们植很多次直到成功为止
I'm gonna do this as many times as it takes to get it right.
不过  事实上  我们只能有一次机会
Well, see, the thing is, we kind of only have one shot.
做一次移植要花一万六千块
Um, it costs $16,000 each time you do this.
为了这次  我们差不多花光了所有的积蓄
So, um, we're kind of using all the money we have to do it just this one time.
天啊
Whoa.
这让我和我的子宫  感觉压力好大
That's... Okay, that's a lot of pressure on me and my uterus.
那么  好吧
So... Well, okay.
也许我能做些什么事  来提高怀孕的机率
So maybe there's something that I can do, you know, just to make sure I get pregnant.
没有  很抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
你还真是什么都不懂
Wow, you guys really don't know anything.
我知道  为什么不让她喝个烂醉
I know. Why doesn't she get drunk?
我很多高中同学  都是这样搞大肚子怀孕的
That worked for a bunch of girls in my high school.
你们几个  知道么  菲比现在
Hey, guys. Do you realize that any minute now...
随时可能会怀孕
...Phoebe could be pregnant?
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
这真是关系一生的大事啊  我知道
It's such a huge, life-altering thing. I know.
考题准备好了
The test is ready.
每一队都要回答十个问题
Okay. Each team will answer 10 questions.
答对最多的队就赢
The first team to answer the most questions wins.
考题项目分类  "恐惧和怪癖"
The categories are "Fears And Pet Peeves"...
"陈年往事"
..."Ancient History"...
"文学"
..."Literature"...
和"日常琐事"
...and "It's All Relative."
现在  扔硬币决定哪队先答
Now, the coin toss, to see who goes first.
好的
Okay.
拜托你们先猜哪一面
Somebody call it this time. Yeah.
字
Tails.
是人头
It's heads. Yeah!
男生队  请挑项目
Gentlemen, pick your category.
"恐惧和怪癖"
"Fears And Pet Peeves."
摩妮卡最受不了什么
"What is Monica's biggest pet peeve?"
动物像人一样穿衣服  答对了
Animals dressed as humans. That's correct.
女生队  同个项目
Ladies? Same category.
好的
Okay.
对于钱德来说  最怕什么
"According to Chandler, what phenomenon scares the bejesus out of him?"
踢踏舞之王麦克费特利
Michael Flatley, Lord of the Dance.
答对了
That is correct.
那个爱尔兰转圈的家伙
The Irish jig guy?
他那双脚跳舞时  好像跟身体分离了一样
His legs flail about as if independent from his body.
男生队  轮到你们了
Gentlemen, your pick.
"日常琐事"
"It's All Relative."
摩妮卡和我的祖母过世时
"Monica and I had a grandmother who died.
两位都参加了她的葬礼
You both went to her funeral.
我们祖母叫什么名字
Name that grandmother."
奶奶  她有真名
Nana? She has a real name.
艾席雅  艾席雅
Althea. Althea?
什么  我蒙的
What are you doing? Took a shot.
你蒙"艾席雅"   "艾席雅"答对了
Shooting with Althea? Althea is correct.
蒙得好
Nice shooting.
"文学"
We'll take "Literature."
乔伊和钱德  每周都会收到《电视周刊》
"Every week, the TV Guide comes to Chandler and Joey's apartment.
请问地址标签上收件人的姓名是什么
What name appears on the address label?"
钱德订的  当然是钱德宾罗
Oh! Chandler gets it. It's Chandler Bing.
不是啦
No.
我恐怕得说《电视周刊》收件人的姓名  是"钱尼德勒邦"
I'm afraid the TV Guide comes to "Chanandler Bong."
我知道这个
I knew that.
瑞秋  用用脑子行不行
Rachel, use your head.
事实上  应该是"钱尼德勒邦小姐"
Actually, it's Miss Chanandler Bong.
嗨  各位小胚胎
Hello, teeny embryos.
我是菲比.布费  嗨
Oh, I'm Phoebe Buffay. Hi.
我的子宫  就是各位未来九个月的家
I'm hoping to be your uterus for the next nine months.
你们应该知道我们这么做  都是为了法兰克和艾莉丝
You should know that we're doing this for Frank and Alice...
你们认识的  你们也曾经在现场
...who you know. You've been there.
他们真的很希望能有个小宝宝
You know, they want you so much.
你们进去之后  要抓住机会
So when you guys get in there, really grab on.
我保证会让你们  住得又舒服又安全
Okay, and I promise that I'll keep you safe and warm
直到你们准备好带你们回家为止
until, you know, you're ready to have them take you home.
所以
So...
这样
Okay.
哦  对了  下次再见面时  如果我尖叫的话  别担心
Oh, and also, next time you see me, if I'm screaming, don't worry.
这只是假定会发生
That's what's supposed to happen.
准备好了吗  呃呃
Ready? Uh-huh?
好运
Good luck.
目前比分是9比8  男生队领先
All right, the score is nine to eight in favor of the guys.
女生队  如果这题答错  男生队就赢了  选一个项目吧
Ladies, if you miss this, the game is theirs. Pick your category.
"日常琐事"
"It's All Relative"!
你不用每次都大喊  对不起
You don't have to shout everything. I'm sorry!
钱德父亲在赌城的滑稽表演  叫做什么名字
Ooh. "What is the name of Chandler's father's..Las Vegas all-male burlesque?"
"同志万岁"
Viva Las Gaygas.
很不幸  答对了
Unfortunately, that is correct.
好啊
Yes.
好的  目前双方平手
All right. We have a tie.
还好  我早有准备了
Luckily, I've prepared for such an event.
抢答赛  喔
The Lightning Round. Ooh.
双方各有30秒抢答
Thirty seconds. All the questions you can answer.
你们输定了
You guys are dead.
我拿手的就是抢答
I am so good at Lightning Rounds.
我大学是主修抢答的  怎么样
I majored in Lightning Rounds, all right?
我们会打垮你  敢不敢赌
We're gonna destroy you. Can want to bet?
怪了  我们这不正是在赌吗
Oh, I'm so confused as to what we've been doing so far.
把赌注提高到  150块如何
How about we play for more money? Say 150?
150块
One hundred and fifty dollars.
200块如何
Say 200?
200块
Two hundred dollars.
你又来了
You're doing it again.
不好意思
Excuse me.
莫妮卡  我不想输200块  我们不会输的
Monica, I don't want to lose $200. We won't.
300块如何  摩妮卡
Okay. Three hundred? Monica.
我只是想让比赛更刺激些
I'm just trying to spice it up.
好  那再加点胡椒粉  别再乱花我的钱了
Okay, so then play for some pepper. Stop spending my money.
我有了
I got it.
我们赢的话  他们就得处理掉那只公鸡
How about if we win, they have to get rid of the rooster.
喔  有意思
Ooh, that's interesting.
嗨  不行  公鸡和我们是一家人
Hey, no way. That rooster's family.
把鸭子也扔了  关鸭子什么事啊  他又不乱叫
Throw in the duck too. What do you have against the duck? It doesn't make noise.
那只鸡被他搞得心浮气躁
Well, he gets the other one all riled up.
听着  我们绝不... 好的  等等
Look, we are not... All right, hold on.
你们赢的话
If you win
我们就处理掉那只鸟儿
we give up the bird. Aah!
我们赢的话
But if we win
就把你们的公寓让给我们
we get your apartment.
哦
Ooh!
成交
Deal!
莫妮卡  拿公寓来赌好像不太稳当
Monica, betting the apartment? I don't know about this.
瑞秋  整个比赛  我没答错一道题
Rachel, I have not missed one question the whole game.
我是抢答之王
I own this game.
看我的手
Look at my hand.
为什么  你手上有答案
Why, do you have the answers written on there?
不是啦  我的手稳得很  你还不放心吗
No. Steady as a rock. Now, are you with me?
好吧  我们上  来吧
All right, let's do it. Come on.Okay.
好的  男生队  先来
All right. Gentlemen, you're up first.
好
Okay.
你们有30秒
You have 30 seconds.
抢答赛开始
The Lightning Round begins
不准跳
Stop it.
开始  莫妮卡当曲棍球守门员时候的绰号
Now. "What was Monica's nickname when she was a field-hockey goalie?"
胖球门  正确
Big Fat Goalie. Correct.
瑞秋说她最喜欢的电影是
"Rachel claims this is her favorite movie."
《危险关系》  正确
Dangerous Liaisons. Correct.
她真正喜欢的电影是  《玩死老弟》  正确
"Her actual favorite is?" Correct. Weekend at Bernie's. Correct.
摩妮卡14岁时  用铅笔扎了她身体的什么部位
"In what part of her body did Monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?"
哦
Oh!
嗯  不是
Ew, no!
是她的耳朵
Her ear.
摩妮卡的毛巾都分门别类  一共分为几类
All right, "Monica categorizes her towels. How many categories are there?"
日常用的  高级毛巾
Okay, everyday use. Fancy.
客用的  高级客用毛巾
Guest. Fancy guest.
还剩两秒钟  11类
Two seconds. Uh, eleven?
11  不可思议  答对了
Eleven. Unbelievable. Eleven is correct.
是的
Yes!
太好了
All right.
男生队答对四题  女士们  准备
That's four for the guys. Ladies, you're up.
好  来吧
All right, all right, come on!
限时抢答30秒
Thirty seconds on the clock.
答对五题你们就赢了
Five correct questions wins the game.
抢答开始  乔伊最喜欢的食物是
The Lightning Round begins now. "What is Joey's favorite food?"
三明治  正确
Sandwiches. Correct.
钱德第一次  碰女生胸部是几岁
"Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?"
14岁 不  19
Fourteen? No, 19.
谢了  老哥
Thanks, man.
乔伊小时有个幻想中的朋友
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
他的名字叫… 莫瑞斯  正确
His name was..." Maurice. Correct.
他的职业是  太空牛仔
"His profession was?" Space cowboy.
正确
Correct.
钱德宾的工作是
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
哦
Oh.
天啊  跟数字有关什么的
Oh, gosh. It has something to do with numbers.
还有处理  他上班带公文包
And processing. And he carries a briefcase.
剩10秒钟  答错就输了
Ten seconds. You need this or you lose the game.
和传送有关的什么
It has something to do with transponding.
他是收发员
Oh! Oh! He's a transponster.
不是一个词能说清楚的
That's not even a word!
我能答  我能答
I can get this. I can get this.
不
No!
好
Yes!
我要摩妮卡的房间  这哪是你说要就要的
I call Monica's room. You can't just call Monica's room.
当然能  先下手为强  谁叫你不先要
Sure I can. Standard Shotgun Rules. I'm in sight of the room and I called it.
可恶
Damn.
我感觉好像要生病了
Man, I feel like I'm coming down with something.
什么
Oh. Yeah.
要不要猜猜我的扁桃腺  是什么颜色  用公寓来赌
Bet you can't guess what color my tonsils are. I bet the apartment.
哦  我才不会拿  这么棒的公寓来赌呢
Oh, I would never bet this apartment. It's too nice.
嗨  菲比  你肚子里有东西了吗
Hey. Ooh, Pheebs, are they in there?
对  胚胎已经放进去了
Um, yeah, uh-huh, I'm implanted.
感觉怎么样  哦  担心死了
How do you feel? Well, freaked.
因为成功的机率不高
Because it turns out the odds are, like, really sucky.
而且法兰克和艾莉丝  只有这次机会
And this is Frank and Alice's, like, only shot.
就好像他们把所有的蛋  都放在我的篮子里
I mean, they are, like, literally putting all their eggs in my basket.
好  但我打赌你一定会成功
Yeah, but I bet it works.
是吗  你要赌多少
Really? How much?
好吧  我现在就去验孕  就现在
All right, I'm gonna go take a pregnancy test right now.
哦喔  这么快就行
Oh, wow. You can tell this soon?
医生说还要等几天
Well, the doctor says it takes a couple days.
但是我的身体  反应总是比西医快一点
But, I mean, my body's always been a little faster than Western medicine, so...
哦  天啊  你们居然以为真能搬进来啊
Oh, my God. I can't believe you guys actually think you're moving in here.
面对现实吧  宝贝
Well, believe it, baby.
我不搬
Well, I'm not moving.
什么
What?
那不过是场愚蠢的赌局  玩玩罢了
No. It was a stupid bet. We were just playing a game.
赌就赌了  哪能不算
You just can't ignore the bet. It's a bet.
你打赌而且你输了  赌输就是输了
You bet on a bet, and if you lose, you lose the bet.
瑞秋  我们非搬不可
Rach, we have to move.
若我们赢了  也会逼他们把鸟儿处理掉
If we had lost, we would have made them get rid of the birds.
好吧  我也不想这样  但说句安慰你的话
All right, look, I hate this as much as you, but if it makes you feel better...
这都是你的错
this is all your fault.
什么  钱纳德.邦
What? Chanandler Bong.
我们每周都偷他们的电视周刊
Come on, we steal that TV Guide every week.
我就知道
I knew it.
我不管  我哪儿也不去
I don't care. I'm not going anywhere.
酷啊  跟女生做室友
Cool. Girl roommate.
怎么样
Well?
没有  现在还没有
Nope, not knocked up yet.
才几个小时  多给它们点时间吧
It's only been a couple hours, so just give it some time.
好吧  这段时间  我是无能为力了
Yeah, all right. Meanwhile, I'm gonna do whatever I can to help this...
我只能躺在你的椅子上  这样
...so I'm just gonna, you know, lie in your chair, okay?
知道么  只能
You know, just...
让地心引力发挥作用
Yeah, good. I'm gonna let gravity, you know, do its jobs.
瑞秋  过来帮我搬这个箱子
Hey, Rach, can you give me a hand with this box?
不  把箱子放下来  我们哪儿都不去
No. Put that box down. We are not going anywhere!
这是我的公寓  我喜欢它
This is my apartment and I like it.
这是女生的公寓
This is a girl's apartment.
那里才是又脏又臭的男生公寓
That is a boy's apartment. It's dirty and it smells.
这个多漂亮  这个太漂亮了
This is pretty. It's so pretty.
看  墙壁是紫的
And look, and it's purple.
我跟你说  稳若盘石的小姐  我不搬
And I'm telling you, you with your steady hand, I am not moving.
而且  我的手现在也稳若盘石了
And now I have got the steady hand.
我去搞定  这就对了
I'll take care of it. That's right.
照我手的话去做
You do what the hand says.
怎么样  我把床垫输掉了
How'd it go? I lost our mattresses.
小胎儿  你在里面吗
Are you in there, little fetus?
九个月后  是否就能够相见
In nine months, will you come greet us?
我会给你们买阿迪达斯的
I will buy you some Adidas
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
嗨  菲比
Oh, hi, Phoebe?
我们刚刚去过药店  给你带了点礼物
Um, we were just at the drugstore, um, so we got you a little present.
哦  是棒棒糖和验孕棒
Um, it's a lollipop and a home pregnancy test.
别搞混了  棒棒糖沾到尿很恶心的
Hey, don't mix those up. You could really ruin that lollipop.
那么  想不想验一下  只是问问
So, um, you feel like taking a test? There's only one question.
好吧  我验就是了  不  我验
All right. I will. No, I will.
但是别忘了  现在测还早
But, um, you know, just remember that it's still really early.
所以如果说我没怀孕  不表示我不会怀孕
Okay, so if it says that I'm not pregnant...that doesn't mean I'm not gonna get pregnant, okay?
所以即使这次没成
And just, please, just so I don't go completely nuts
也别觉得所有希望都没了
just try not to put all your hopes on this, okay?
好
Okay.
好极了
Great.
你知道么  你们真是坏到骨子里去了
You know what? You are mean boys who are just being mean.
别对我们发火  没人逼你们
Hey, don't get mad at us. No one forced you to raise the stakes.
不对  她  她逼我
That is not true. She did. She forced me.
要是你没答错的话  我们还能在这住
We'd still be here if you hadn't got the question wrong.
那些个问题太愚蠢了  太不公平了
Well, it was a stupid, unfair question!
别怪我出的问题
Don't blame the questions!
别在我们家大吵大闹
Would you all stop yelling in our apartment?
扫了我们的搬家的兴趣
You are ruining moving day for us.
别说这里是你们家  本来就是
Would you stop calling it your apartment? It is ours.
你们  你们  你们要有孩子了
Guys, you guys, you're gonna have a baby.
他们要有孩子了
They're gonna have a baby.
我姐姐要帮我生小孩了
My sister's going to have my baby!
别抱了  这对宝宝不好
Okay, but this can't be good for the baby.
我找不到垃圾袋了
I can't find garbage bags.
这里面我好像看到有
Oh, I think I saw some in here.
什么东西
What is it?
不知道  要是把抽屉关上  他也许会死
I don't know. But maybe if we keep that drawer shut, it'll die.
真不敢相信我们竟然住在这种地方
I can't believe we're living here.
什么事  怎么了
What? What is it?
你看到储藏室有多大了吗
Did you see the size of the closets?!
真不敢相信咱们可以住在这里
I can't believe we live here.